At the end of the world, the adventure begins.
Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End is a adventure,
fantasy, action film directed by Gore Verbinski.
Captain Jack Sparrow, that wily charmer of a pirate, is trapped in Davy Jones' Locker
when his pirate brethren begin a desperate quest to locate and rescue him.
Follow their wild seafaring adventures from exotic
Singapore to World's End and beyond.
Jack Sparrow, played by Johnny Depp.
Barbossa, played by Geoffrey Rush.
Will Turner, played by Orlando Bloom.
Elizabeth Swann, played by Keira Knightley.
Norrington, played by Jack Davenport.
Davy Jones, played by Bill Nighy.
Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End is a 2007 American epic fantasy swashbuckler film directed by
Gore Verbinski, produced by Jerry Bruckheimer, and written by Ted Elliott and Terry Rossio.
The direct sequel to Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest (2006), it is the third installment in the Pirates of the Caribbean film series, and follows an urgent quest to locate and
save Captain Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp), trapped on a sea of sand in Davy Jones' Locker, and convene the Brethren Court in a war against the East India Trading Company.
In an uneasy alliance, Will Turner (Orlando Bloom), Elizabeth Swann (Keira Knightley), Hector Barbossa (Geoffrey Rush), and the
Black Pearl crew rescue Jack and prepare to fight Lord Cutler Beckett, who controls Davy Jones and the Flying Dutchman.
Two sequels to Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl were conceived in 2004,
with Elliott and Rossio developing a story arc that would span both films.
The film was shot in two shoots during 2005 and 2006, the
former of which was released as Dead Man's Chest.
This also marks the final film of the series to be directed by Verbinski.
With a production budget of US$300 million, it was the most
expensive film ever made at the time of its release.
At World's End premiered at the Disneyland Resort on May 19, 2007, then
theatrically released in the United States on May 25.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, but was the
highest-grossing film of 2007, bringing in over $963 million.
It was nominated at the 80th Academy Awards for Best Makeup and Best Visual Effects,
and won Favorite Movie Actor for Depp at the 2008 Kids' Choice Awards.
A standalone sequel,  On Stranger Tides, was released in 2011.
Dead Men Tell No Tales, released in 2017, followed as a
direct continuation of At World's End.
The film explores themes of exotic island, strong woman,
love of one's life, afterlife, traitor.
The tone is lighthearted.